[
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§Œ",
        "response": "ğŸ§Œ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¥·",
        "response": "ğŸ¥·"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸš€",
        "response": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸš€"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§Š",
        "response": "ğŸ§Š"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¥£",
        "response": "ğŸ¥£"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«˜",
        "response": "ğŸ«˜"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒ½",
        "response": "ğŸŒ½"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ´â€â˜ ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ´â€â˜ ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¬",
        "response": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¬"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸƒ",
        "response": "ğŸƒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ•—",
        "response": "ğŸ•—"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ“£",
        "response": "ğŸ“£"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ”ï¸",
        "response": "âœ”ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸš¹",
        "response": "ğŸš¹"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒ€",
        "response": "ğŸŒ€"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™»ï¸",
        "response": "â™»ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ–Œï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ–Œï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ“",
        "response": "ğŸ“"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ“¯",
        "response": "ğŸ“¯"
    },
    {
        "question": "âš–ï¸",
        "response": "âš–ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§²",
        "response": "ğŸ§²"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’",
        "response": "ğŸ’"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¡",
        "response": "ğŸ’¡"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ–±ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ–±ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒƒ",
        "response": "ğŸŒƒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›±ï¸",
        "response": "â›±ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ›¸",
        "response": "ğŸ›¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœˆï¸",
        "response": "âœˆï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§",
        "response": "ğŸ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¥…",
        "response": "ğŸ¥…"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‘",
        "response": "ğŸ‘‘"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’‡â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ’‡â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸ’»",
        "response": "ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸ’»"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¥€",
        "response": "ğŸ¥€"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦š",
        "response": "ğŸ¦š"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŸ",
        "response": "ğŸŸ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸª±",
        "response": "ğŸª±"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦",
        "response": "ğŸ¦"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦â€â¬›",
        "response": "ğŸ¦â€â¬›"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸï¸",
        "response": "ğŸï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ®",
        "response": "ğŸ®"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸª",
        "response": "ğŸª"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŠ",
        "response": "ğŸŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›¸ï¸",
        "response": "â›¸ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "ğŸ”¥"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒªï¸",
        "response": "ğŸŒªï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜„ï¸",
        "response": "â˜„ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "â›„",
        "response": "â›„"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸŒ¸",
        "response": "ğŸŒ¸"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸš",
        "response": "ğŸš"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸŒ",
        "response": "ğŸŒ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ§",
        "response": "ğŸ§"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¶",
        "response": "ğŸ¶"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜•",
        "response": "â˜•"
    },
    {
       "question": "âš¡",
        "response": "âš¡"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸŒ¬ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸŒ¬ï¸"
    },
    {
       "question": "âœ¨",
        "response": "âœ¨"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸŒ‹",
        "response": "ğŸŒ‹"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ„ğŸ»",
        "response": "ğŸ„ğŸ»"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ”°",
        "response": "ğŸ”°"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ’°",
        "response": "ğŸ’°"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¦¦",
        "response": "ğŸ¦¦"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ—¿",
        "response": "ğŸ—¿"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¦",
        "response": "ğŸ¦"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ¤",
       "response": "ğŸ¤"
}
]
